{
    "id": "ceafe78ab21e4595acadd5d877291130",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You are old enough to ..................... your own bed now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "make",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You saw James, ......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did you",
                "didn't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If I …………………. enough time tomorrow, I will come and see you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "will have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I would get up earlier if there ..................... a good reason to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This time tomorrow I ...................... on the beach.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will lie",
                "will be lying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever watched ................. cats wash each other?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "how",
                "the way"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She began ……………….. when she was just",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "working",
                "to work",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired ………………… waiting for people who never turn up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Look …………………. the mirror before you drive off.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a …………………. experience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "magic",
                "magical"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}